Guide to the American political campaigns miscellany, 1868-2016
American political campaigns miscellany
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
American political campaigns miscellany, 1868-2016 [bulk 1968-1980].
6477
1314 items.
Correspondence, Memorabilia, Printed Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Print, broadside, ribbon, posters, buttons, bumper stickers, bubble gum, greeting card, headscarf, medal, postcards and inaugural programs from various political campaigns, both national and gubernatorial (New York State).
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Print, broadside, ribbon, posters, buttons, bumper stickers, bubble gum, greeting card, headscarf, medal, postcards and inaugural programs from various political campaigns, both national and gubernatorial (New York State). The ribbon is from Ulysses S. Grant's 1868 presidential campaign. The medal is from Dwight D. Eisenhower and Richard M. Nixon's inauguration in 1957. The programs are from the inauguration of Franklin D. Roosevelt and John N. Garner in 1937 and Dwight D. Eisenhower and Richard M. Nixon in 1953. The postcards are from the 2000 campaign with Al and Tipper Gore and Joe Lieberman. The buttons and bumper stickers are from the following campaigns: Nader and LaDuke 2000, Gore and Lieberman 2000, George W. Bush 2000, John Kerry 2004 bumper sticker, Ford and Dole, Richard Nixon, and Jim Buckley. Anti-Bush buttons, and donkey and elephant "ABB" (anybody but Bush) pins created by artist Courtney Peterson. Also included is Presidential Elections of the 20th Century as reported on the front page of the New York Times. Also items from exhibition for 2004. Also, countdown clock from January 2008. election.
Mule-mounted tin and cast iron Ballot Box, ca. 1868.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Clinton, Bill, 1946-; Ferraro, Geraldine.; Mondale, Walter F., 1928-; Bush, George W.(George Walker), 1946-; Eisenhower, Dwight D.(Dwight David), 1890-1969.; Garner, John Nance, 1868-1967.; Gore, Albert, 1948-; Gore, Tipper, 1948-; Lieberman, Joseph, 1942-; Nader, Ralph.; Nixon, Richard M.(Richard Milhous), 1913-; Roosevelt, Franklin D.(Franklin Delano), 1882-1945.
Subjects:
Political campaigns--United States.; Political campaigns--New York (State); Campaign paraphernalia.; Elections.; Presidents--United States--Election.; Campaign insignia.
Places:
New York (State)--Politics and government.; United States--Politics and government.
Form and Genre Terms:
Broadsides.; Bumper stickers.; Buttons (information artifacts).; Political posters.; Prints.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Ballots
Boxes 18, 19
Series II. Books
Box 20
Series III. Bric-a-Brac
Boxes 4, 6, 17, 18, 26, 27
Series IV. Broadsides
Boxes 1, 2, 17-19, 23, 26, 28, mapcase
Series V. Buttons
Boxes 3-5, 21, 24-27
Series VI. Cartoons
Box 19
Series VII. Maps & Charts
Box 19
Series VIII. Pamphlets
Boxes 9-11, 17, 18, 28, mapcase
Series IX. Paper Miscellaneous
Boxes 7, 8, 27, 28
Series X. Parades
Box 18
Series XI. Posters
Box 19, mapcase
Series XII. Prints
Boxes 17, 19, mapcase
Series XIII. Ribbons
Boxes 14, 17
Series XIV. Scrapbooks
Box 15
Series XV. Sheet Music
Box 19
Series XVI. Songbooks
Box 19
Series XVII. Textiles
Boxes 16-18, mapcase
Series XVIII. Trinkets
Boxes 12, 13
Series XIX. Wearing Apparel
Boxes 14, 17, 18, 22
Series XX. Sound Recordings
Box 20
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Ballots
  - Sample Ballot For Presidential Election 1912, 1912; 6477.BA0001; Items: 1 (Box 18)
    Candidate: n/a
    Election: 1912
    Party: n/a
  - Vote For Woman Suffrage First (Sample of Amendment Number 1), 1917; 6477.BA0002; Items: 1 (Box 19)
    Election: 1917
  - Follow the Star Regular Democratic Candidates (Sample Ballot), 1916; 6477.BA0003; Items: 1 (Box 19)
    Election: 1916
    Party: Democratic
  - Absentee Ballot Application and Registration Forms, n/a; 6477.BA0004; Items: 8 (Box 19)
    Election: n/a
  - Ballot For Presidential Election, 1964 (City of Ithaca, Ward 2), 1964; 6477.BA0005; Items: 1 (Box 18)
    Election: 1964
  - Cast Your Vote For Buckley First! (Sample Ballot), ca. 1970; 6477.BA0006; Items: 2 (Box 19)
    Candidate: Buckley, James L.
    Election: 1970
    Party: Conservative
  - Buckley For Senator Watcher's Certificate; Instruction And Report Sheet, 1970; 6477.BA0007; Items: 2 (Box 19)
  - Specimen Ballot General Election...1976...Lake County, Illinois, 1976; 6477.BA0008; Items: 1 (Box 19)
    Election: 1976
  - Application For A N.Y. State Military Ballot & Party Enrollment, ca. 1980; 6477.BA0009; Items: 1 (Box 19)
    Election: 1980
  - Photocopy Of Ballot For Town Of Caroline, 1980; 6477.BA0010; Items: 1 (Box 19)
- Series II. Books
  - Democratic Fact Book 1968, 1968; 6477.BK0001; Items: 1 (Box 20)
    Candidate: Humphrey, Hubert H.
    Election: 1968
  - Factual Campaign Information, 1972; 6477.BK0002; Items: 1 (Box 20)
    Election: 1972
  - State of New York: A Memorial to Theodore Roosevelt, 1919; 6477.BK003; Items: 1 (Box 20)
    Candidate: Roosevelt, Theodore
    Party: Republican
  - Proceedings of the Legislature of the State of New York Relative to the Life and Services of William McKinley, 1902; 6477.BK0004; Items: 1 (Box 20)
    Candidate: McKinley, William
  - The Johnson Years, 1969; 6477.BK0005; Items: 1 (Box 20)
    Candidate: Johnson, Lyndon B.
  - How To Win in 1952 Campaign Handbook Democratic National Committee, 1952; 6477.BK0006; Items: 1 (Box 20)
    Candidate: Stevenson, Adlai E.
    Election: 1952
  - The Facts About La Follette And Wheeler, 1924; 6477.BK0007; Items: 1 (Box 20)
    Candidate: LaFollette, Robert Marion
    Election: 1924
    Party: Progressive
  - None Dare Call It Treason (By John A. Stormer), 1964; 6477.BK0008; Items: 2 (Box 20)
  - A Choice Not An Echo (By Phyllis Schlafly), 1964; 6477.BK0009; Items: 1 (Box 20)
  - Where I Stand (By Senator Barry Goldwater), 1964; 6477.BK0010; Items: 1 (Box 20)
    Candidate: Goldwater, Barry M.
  - We Like Ike: The Eisenhower Presidency And 1950's America (Organized by J. Richard Gruber), 1990; 6477.BK0011; Items: 1 (Box 20)
    Candidate: Eisenhower, Dwight D.
  - Official Souvenir Program Inaugural Ceremonies March 4 1901, 1901; 6477.BK0012; Items: 1 (Box 20)
    Election: 1900
- Series III. Bric-a-Brac
  - Eisenhower "I Like Ike"/G.O.P. Elephant License Plate, ca. 1952; 6477.BB0001; Items: 1 (Box 6)
  - Key to the City of Seattle, ca. 1889-1980; 6477.BB0002; Items: 1 (Box 6)
    Candidate: Washington, George
    Party: Federalist
  - "You Win With Gore" Bubble-gum Cigar, ca. 2000; 6477.BB0003; Items: 1 (Box 6)
    Candidate: Gore, Albert A.
    Election: 2000
  - "Hillary...My No. 1" Bubble-gum Cigar, ca. 2000; 6477.BB0004; Items: 1 (Box 6)
    Candidate: Clinton, Hillary Rodham
  - "Vote Republican" Plastic Bag, ca. 1970-2002; 6477.BB0005; Items: 1 (Box 6)
  - G.O.P. Antenna Flag, 1968; 6477.BB0006; Items: 1 (Box 6)
    Candidate: Nixon, Richard M.
  - Humphrey Campaign Recordings, 1968; 6477.BB0007; Items: 6 (Box 6)
  - "Nixon's The One" Phonograph Record, 1968; 6477.BB0008; Items: 1 (Box 6)
  - "Spiro T. Agnew Speaks Out" Phonograph Record, ca. 1968; 6477.BB0009; Items: 1 (Box 6)
    Candidate: Agnew, Spiro T.
  - Pressed Paper Plaque of President McKinley, ca. 1901; 6477.BB0010; Items: 1 (Box 6)
  - "Six Presidents Speak - A Profile of the Presidency" (phonograph record with jacket), 1972; 6477.BB0011; Items: 1 (Box 17)
    Candidate: various
    Party: Democratic; Republican
  - Small "Hoover" Flag on a Stick, ca. 1928-1932; 6477.BB0012; Items: 1 (Box 17)
    Candidate: Hoover, Herbert C.
    Election: 1928;1932
  - McCarthy Matchbook with Photo, ca. 1968; 6477.BB0013; Items: 1 (Box 4)
    Candidate: McCarthy, Eugene J.
    Party: New
  - Glass Slides: Charles W. Fairbanks; Charles Evans Hughes; Charles S. Whitman & Edward Schoeneck, ca. 1916; 6477.BB0014; Items: 3 (Box 4)
  - "Let's Do something About It Elect Alex Forger For State Senate (Shopping Bag), n/a; 6477.BB0015; Items: 1 (Box 18)
    Candidate: Forger, Alexander D.
  - "Support Wendell Ford For Governor" (Shopping Bag), ca. 1970; 6477.BB0016; Items: 1 (Box 18)
    Candidate: Ford, Wendell H.
  - "Carter's Nuts" (Paper bag printed with grinning peanuts), ca. 1976-1980; 6477.BB0017; Items: 1 (Box 6)
    Candidate: Carter, Jimmy
    Election: 1976; 1980
  - Jimmy Carter Inaugural Peanuts, 1977; 6477.BB0018; Items: 1 (Box 4)
  - "Get A Grip On Good Government. Elect Weicker For Congress( Rubber Jar Opener), ca. 1968; 6477.BB0019; Items: 1 (Box 6)
    Candidate: Weicker, Lowell
  - "It's time for A Change! Elect Councilman Roger Ladd To Congress" (Car Trash-bag), ca. 1968; 6477.BB0020; Items: 1 (Box 6)
    Candidate: Ladd, Roger
  - "Let's Do Something...Vote For Dave Harris For Congress" (Red Balloon), n/a; 6477.BB0021; Items: 1 (Box 4)
    Candidate: Harris, Dave
  - "W. Shatas Big Elephant Club" White Letters on Black Plastic Elephant Shape, ca. 1950; 6477.BB0022; Items: 1 (Box 4)
    Election: 1950
  - Wooden Stake (Pointed At Bottom, Top Half Painted Bright Blue, 18-1/4" x 1" x 1"), n/a; 6477.BB0023; Items: 1 (Box 6)
  - "Robison Is My Congressman" (Balloons; one red, one blue), ca. 1964; 6477.BB0024; Items: 2 (Box 4)
    Candidate: Robison, Howard W.
  - Robison Is My Congressman He Measures Up To the Job (Wooden Ruler), ca. 1964; 6477.BB0025; Items: 1 (Box 6)
  - Re-Elect GOP Candidate Metcalf For State Senate (Matchbooks), ca. 1964; 6477.BB0026; Items: 2 (Box 4)
    Candidate: Metcalf, George R.
  - Connie Cook For New York State Assembly (Matchbook), ca. 1964; 6477.BB0027; Items: 2 (Box 4)
    Candidate: Cook, Constance E.
  - Keating. New York State's Man (Phonograph record with jacket), ca. 1964; 6477.BB0028; Items: 24 (Box 6)
    Candidate: Keating, Kenneth B.
  - Nixon for President (Matchbook), ca. 1960; 6477.BB0029; Items: 1 (Box 4)
    Election: 1960
  - Vote for Francis J. "Bud" Souhan...Congress 36th District (Matchbook), ca. 1960; 6477.BB0030; Items: 2 (Box 4)
    Candidate: Souhan, Francis J.
  - F.D.R. Matchbook (Initials worked into sailboat design, gold on dark blue cover), n/a; 6477.BB0031; Items: 1 (Box 4)
    Candidate: Roosevelt, Frederick D.
  - Re-Elect Cook For Assembly (Plastic Bottle Caps), ca. 1970; 6477.BB0032; Items: 5 (Box 4)
  - Let's Work Together For A Cleaner New York -Nelson A. Rockefeller (Plastic Bag), ca. 1970; 6477.BB0033; Items: 1 (Box 6)
    Candidate: Rockefeller, Nelson A.
  - Independents for Rockefeller (Plastic Tote Bags), ca. 1970; 6477.BB0034; Items: 2 (Box 18)
  - Rocky Rocky Rocky...(Plastic tote Bags), ca. 1970; 6477.BB0035; Items: 2 (Box 18)
  - Lefkowitz Attorney General (Plastic Bag), ca. 1970; 6477.BB0036; Items: 1 (Box 18)
    Candidate: Lefkowitz, Lewis J.
  - United Transportation Union Pencil Clip, n/a; 6477.BB0037; Items: 1 (Box 4)
  - Eugene McCarthy For President (Phonograph Record...by Peter, Paul And Mary), ca. 1968; 6477.BB0038; Items: 2 (Box 6)
  - McCarthy For President (Large Paper Shopping Bag), ca. 1968; 6477.BB0039; Items: 1 (Box 18)
  - McHugh For Congress (Balloons; one red, one blue), ca. 1976; 6477.BB0040; Items: 2 (Box 6)
    Candidate: McHugh, Matthew
  - Bill Smith Red Balloon, ca. 1980; 6477.BB0041; Items: 1 (Box 4)
    Candidate: Smith, William T.
  - Re-Elect Congressman Gary Lee (White Plastic Bag), ca. 1980; 6477.BB0042; Items: 1 (Box 6)
    Candidate: Lee, Gary
  - Bush-Quayle squeeze toy, 1988; 6477.BB0043; Items: 1 (Box 6)
    Candidate: Bush, George and Daniel Quayle
    Election: 1988
  - Vote Soap, Vote/Feel Good, ca. 1980; 6477.BB0044; Items: 2 (Box 6)
    Election: 2004
  - Reagan-Bush Inauguration (White Plastic Bag), 1985; 6477.BB0045; Items: 1 (Box 6)
    Candidate: Reagan,Ronald and George Bush
    Election: 1984
  - Dukakis Presidential Favorites (bubble gum cigars)), 1988; 6477.BB0046; Items: 1 (Box 6)
    Candidate: Dukakis, Michael
    Party: Democrat
  - Smart Women elect to make a difference election kit [League of Women Voters] (tattoos, bumper sticker, pencil, pad, magnet, button, leaflet), 2004; 6477.BB0047; Items: several (Box 6)
  - Backwards Bush countdown clock 2008, 2008; 6477.BB0048; Items: 1 (Box 6)
    Election: 2008
  - "Bob McMillan for Senate" Balloon, 6477.BB0049; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: McMillan, Bob
    Election:
    Party:
  - Moynihan Balloon, 6477.BB0050; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Moynihan
  - "Elect Ford/Dole" Keychain, 1976; 6477.BB0051; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Ford/Dole
  - "Bob McMillan US Senate" magnet, 6477.BB0052; Items: 1 (Box 26)
  - "Shulze for Congress" Magnet, 6477.BB0053; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Shulze
  - Beryl Anthony nail file, 6477.BB0054; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Anthony, Beryl
  - Pins with Greek letters, 6477.BB0055; Items: 2 (Box 26)
  - American Airlines wings, 6477.BB0056; Items: 2 (Box 26)
  - McCarthy key chain, 1968; 6477.BB0057; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: McCarthy
  - Buffalo Nickel, 1936; 6477.BB0058; Items: 1 (Box 26)
  - Carter/Mondale Key chain, 1976; 6477.BB0059; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Carter/Mondale
  - NY Hard Rock Cafe pin, 6477.BB0060; Items: 1 (Box 26)
  - Beryl Anthony Pencil, 6477.BB0061; Items: 1 (Box 26)
  - Bob McMillan Pencil, 6477.BB0062; Items: 1 (Box 26)
  - Nixon Now Matchbook, 6477.BB0063; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate:Nixon, Richard
  - I Like Ike Matchbook, 6477.BB0064; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Eisenhower
  - LBJ for President Matchbook, 6477.BB0065; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Johnson, Lyndon
  - Reagan/Bush Matchbook, 1984; 6477.BB0066; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Reagan, Ronald and Bush, George
  - Ronald Reagan Whitehouse Matchbook, 6477.BB0067; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Reagan, Ronald
  - Goldwater Matchbook, 6477.BB0068; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Goldwater
  - Carey for Governor Card, 6477.BB0069; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Carey, Hugh
  - Humphrey/Muskie Card, 6477.BB0070; Items: 1 (Box 26)
    Candidate: Humphrey/Muskie
  - Mule-mounted tin and cast iron Ballot Box, ca. 1868; MU-2017; Items: 1
  - Miscellaneous Obama items, 6477.BB0071; Items: 4 (Box 27)
    Candidate: Obama, Barack
- Series IV. Broadsides
  - "Nixon for President" Bumper Sticker, ca. 1960-1972; 6477.BR0001; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
    Election: 1960, 1968, 1972
  - Blazer for Congress, n/a; 6477.BR0002; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder U-4)
    Candidate: Blazer
  - "President Nixon. Now more than ever." Bumper Sticker, ca. 1972; 6477.BR0003; Items: 3 (Box 2)
  - Ford-Dole Bumper Sticker, ca. 1976; 6477.BR0004; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Ford, Gerald R.
  - "Jim Buckley The Senator" Bumper Sticker, ca. 1968-1980; 6477.BR0005; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Buckley, James Lane
    Election: 1968; 1970; 1976; 1980
    Party: Conservative; Republican
  - Gore-Lieberman Bumper Stickers, 2000; 6477.BR0006; Items: 4 (Box 2)
  - Nader-LaDuke Bumper Stickers, ca. 2000; 6477.BR0007; Items: 2 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Nader, Ralph
    Party: Green
  - "McCarthy for President" Bumper Sticker, ca. 1968; 6477.BR0008; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - "Stop Nixon" Sticker, ca. 1960-1972; 6477.BR0009; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Election: 1960; 1968; 1972
  - "Snoopy For President" Advertisement for Millbrook Breads, 1972; 6477.BR0010; Items: 2 (Box 17)
  - McGovern Bumper Sticker, ca. 1972; 6477.BR0011; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Candidate: McGovern, George S.
  - "Another Teacher For McGovern" Bumper Sticker, ca. 1972; 6477.BR0012; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - "President Nixon" Bumper Sticker, ca. 1972; 6477.BR0013; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - McGovern Sign, ca. 1972; 6477.BR0014; Items: 1 (Box 18)
  - McGovern Campaign Fact Sheets, ca. 1972; 6477.BR0015; Items: 9 (Box 2)
  - McGovern For President, ca. 1972; 6477.BR0016; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - "Go ahead, Mr. Nixon,", ca. 1972; 6477.BR0017; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - "Can you stand four more years...", ca. 1972; 6477.BR0018; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - "50,000 lives ago.", ca. 1972; 6477.BR0019; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - McGovern-Shriver Shoppers' Guide, ca. 1972; 6477.BR0020; Items: 1 (Box 17)
  - McCarthy Campaign Comes To Ithaca, ca. 1968; 6477.BR0021; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - McCarthy on Vietnam, ca. 1968; 6477.BR0022; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - ..."Give A Republican Gift", 1968; 6477.BR0023; Items: 2 (Box 2)
  - On Making a Rational Choice in 1968, 1968; 6477.BR0024; Items: 5 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Rockefeller, Nelson
  - Letter to the Cornell Daily Sun, ca. 1968; 6477.BR0025; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - "Will the Real Morris Noss Please Stand Up?", ca. 1967; 6477.BR0026; Items: 3 (Box 2)
    Candidate: O'Mara
    Election: 1967
  - Cutout Letters Spelling EAGLETON (Likeley used in public presentation), ca. 1972; 6477.BR0027; Items: 8 (Box 18)
    Candidate: Eagleton, Thomas F.
  - McCarthy For President Rally, ca. 1968; 6477.BR0028; Items: 1 (Box 19)
  - Tompkins County Democrats For McCarthy Invite You..., ca. 1968; 6477.BR0029; Items: 1 (Box 18)
  - Peace: Is The War Really Over?? (Anti-Nixon), ca. 1972; 6477.BR0030; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Ithaca School Board Election Flyer, n/a; 6477.BR0031; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - "McCarthy For President" Bumper Sticker, ca. 1968; 6477.BR0032; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Humphrey Bumper Sticker, ca. 1968; 6477.BR0033; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Romney Stickers, 1968; 6477.BR0034; Items: 4 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Romney, George W.
  - Mondale-Ferraro Bumper Sticker, ca. 1984; 6477.BR0035; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Mondale, Walter
  - "Wallace for President" Bumper Sticker, ca. 1964-1968; 6477.BR0036; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Wallace, George
    Election: 1964; 1968
    Party: Democratic; Independent
  - Humphrey-Muskie Sticker, ca. 1968; 6477.BR0037; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - American Flag Lapel Pin and Advertisement for Promotional Use, n/a; 6477.BR0038; Items: 2 (Box 2)
  - "Ray Gabler, Congress 10th District" (Bumper Sticker), ca. 1968; 6477.BR0039; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Gabler, Ray
  - "Miller For Congress" (Bumper Sticker), ca. 1968; 6477.BR0040; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Miller, Howard
  - "I'm Backing America Douglas S. Warren For Congress" (Bumper Sticker), n/a; 6477.BR0041; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Warren, Douglas S.
  - "James Farmer For Congress" (Bumper Sticker), ca. 1968; 6477.BR0042; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Farmer, James
  - "Philosopher Speaks of Peace...", ca. 1952; 6477.BR0043; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Lamont, Corliss
    Party: American Labor
  - Adlai E. Stevenson for President..., ca. 1952-1956; 6477.BR0044; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Election: 1952; 1956
  - Time for A Change?, ca. 1952; 6477.BR0045; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Don't Let the GOPlins Get You!, n/a; 6477.BR0046; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - You Are The Victim Of Republican High Prices...Vote For Democrats, ca. 1952; 6477.BR0047; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Move Forward With Stevenson And Sparkman..., ca. 1952; 6477.BR0048; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Federal Employees Represent You!, ca. 1952; 6477.BR0049; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Boomerang! Truman's Big Lie Bites Him Back, ca. 1952; 6477.BR0050; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Attention Wage Earners! General Eisenhower Says..., 1952; 6477.BR0051; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Warning! You Must Register If You Want To Vote!, ca. 1956; 6477.BR0052; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Election: 1956
  - Who Is The Safe Man?, ca. 1908; 6477.BR0053; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Bryan, William J.
    Election: 1908
  - Woodrow Wilson College Men's League, 1912; 6477.BR0054; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Wilson, Woodrow
  - One Hundred Million (A Statement from National Hughes Alliance), ca. 1916; 6477.BR0055; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Hughes, Charles E.
  - Headquarters State League Of Independent Democratic Clubs..., ca. 1916; 6477.BR0056; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Branch Chairmen Of the Hughes National College League, ca. 1916; 6477.BR0057; Items: 1 (Box 2)
  - Your Party And Your Pocket Book, ca. 1920; 6477.BR0058; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Cox, James M.
    Election: 1920
  - Dollars Or Dead Boys?, ca. 1920; 6477.BR0059; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - How You Can Help (League Of Nations), ca. 1920; 6477.BR0060; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - The Suffrage Planks, n/a; 6477.BR0061; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - We Oppose Woman Suffrage, n/a; 6477.BR0062; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Mr. Voter: Your Candidate...Believes In Votes For Women, 1917; 6477.BR0063; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Special Privileges New York Women Enjoy Now, ca. 1915; 6477.BR0064; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Population Votes - Area Does Not, ca. 1914; 6477.BR0065; Items: 1 (Box 18)
  - Proposed Debate (Syracuse Dist. Anti-Saloon League), n/a; 6477.BR0066; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - What Chancellor Day Of Syracuse University Says of Governor Glynn, ca. 1914; 6477.BR0067; Items: 2 (Box 1)
    Candidate: Glynn, Martin H.
    Election: 1914
  - Martin H. Glynn Repays the Farmers For Cattle Destroyed, 1913; 6477.BR0068; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Martin H. Glynn Comptroller...Not Dependent Upon Politics For Livelihood, ca. 1908; 6477.BR0069; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Assemblyman McDaniels Answers The Petty Falsehoods..., 1911; 6477.BR0070; Items: 1 (Box 1)
    Candidate: McDaniels, Minor
    Election: 1911
  - The President Wants Palmer, ca. 1916; 6477.BR0071; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Palmer, Frederick W.
  - "Travis A Lap Dog For Whitman" Says Masters In Attack, 1916; 6477.BR0072; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Masters, Joseph W.
  - Judge Seabury Strong Man, ca. 1916; 6477.BR0073; Items: 1 (Box 18)
    Candidate: Seabury, Samuel
  - Senator Halliday's Efficiency Shown By His Official Record, ca. 1916; 6477.BR0074; Items: 1 (Box 17)
    Candidate: Banfield, Mark
  - President Of The Ingersoll-Rand Urges Palmer For Congress, ca. 1916; 6477.BR0075; Items: 1 (Box 18)
  - Jim Snyder For Congress (Sticker), ca. 1982; 6477.BR0076; Items: 1 (Box 1)
    Candidate: Snyder, James
    Election: 1982
  - Boehlert 25th Congressional District Of New York, ca. 1982; 6477.BR0077; Items: 1 (Box 1)
    Candidate: Boehlert, Sherwood L.
  - Dave Crowley For Congress, ca. 1982; 6477.BR0078; Items: 1 (Box 1)
    Candidate: Crowley, David
  - Crowley For Congress (Bumper sticker), ca. 1982; 6477.BR0079; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Lehrman Governor (Bumper sticker), ca. 1982; 6477.BR0080; Items: 1 (Box 1)
    Candidate: Lehrman, Lewis E.
  - Lower Taxes Lehrman Governor (Bumper sticker), ca. 1982; 6477.BR0081; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Lewis E. Lehrman, ca. 1982; 6477.BR0082; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Fran Sclafani For Attorney General, ca. 1982; 6477.BR0083; Items: 1 (Box 1)
    Candidate: Sclafani, Frances A.
  - McHugh For Congress (Bumper sticker), ca. 1982; 6477.BR0084; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Moynihan (Sticker), ca. 1982; 6477.BR0085; Items: 1 (Box 1)
    Candidate: Moynihan, Daniel Patrick
  - Senator Moynihan (Bumper sticker)Snyder, ca. 1982; 6477.BR0086; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Cuomo [Heart] NY...All Of It! (Bumper sticker), ca. 1982; 6477.BR0087; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Cuomo, Mario M
  - Vote For Snyder Congress, ca. 1982; 6477.BR0088; Items: 1 (Box 2)
    Candidate: Snyder
  - 50th NY State Senatorial District Vote Shay, ca. 1982; 6477.BR0089; Items: 1 (Box 1)
    Candidate: Shay, Richard J.
  - Jobs - The Bottom Line, n/a; 6477.BR0090; Items: 1 (Box 1)
    Candidate: Joseph, Tim
    Party: Citizens
  - Vote For The Democratic Team, ca. 1982; 6477.BR0091; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Matt McHugh For Congress, ca. 1982; 6477.BR0092; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Carl McCall Lt. Governor, ca. 1982; 6477.BR0093; Items: 1 (Box 1)
    Candidate: McCall, Carl
  - Jobs For New Yorkers, ca. 1982; 6477.BR0094; Items: 1 (Box 1)
    Candidate: Cuomo, Mario M.
  - A New Era For Agriculture, ca. 1982; 6477.BR0095; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Meet The Next Governor Mario Cuomo, ca. 1982; 6477.BR0096; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Mario Cuomo was For The Full 7.4% Social Security C.O.L.A. Increase, ca. 1982; 6477.BR0097; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Mario Cuomo..., ca. 1982; 6477.BR0098; Items: 1 (Box 1)
  - Where Do Your State Candidates Stand...Nuclear Weapons Freeze?, 1982; 6477.BR0099; Items: 1 (Box 1)